Matthew

Hosang-Rose

An agile and solution-oriented programmer skilled in developing full stack web applications. Able to enhance functionality, resolve issues, and modernize websites. Committed to collaborative work dynamics and exceeding business objectives by consistently delivering exceptional value and client experiences.

Web Developer

CONTACTS



Toronto, Ontario 647-896-6277



matthewhosangrose@gmail.com



<u>LinkedIn</u> GitHub



<u>Portfolio</u>

EDUCATION

CS50 Web Programming

Computer Science Harvard University

Nov 2022 - Current

Data Analyst Program

IBM Professional Certificate NPower Canada Feb 2021 - May 2021

Bachelor of Commerce

Business Technology Management Ryerson University Sep 2016 - Apr 2020

SKILLS

HTML Python

CSS Java

JavaScript TypeScript

VueJS Solidity

ReactJS Firebase

NextJS Prompt Engineering

EXPERIENCE

Fully Stacked Bootcamp

Obsidi Academy I Sept 2022 - Dec 2022

A 3 month intensive bootcamp that goes over the fundamentals of object oriented programming

- · Trained in advanced data structures and algorithms with time and space complexity
- · Manipulated PostgreSQL databases with Java frameworks like Spring
- Developed full stack web applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and integrated APIs with frameworks such as Spring and Hibernate

Frontend Mastery Bootcamp

Clever Programmer I Dec 2021 - May 2022

A 5 month intensive bootcamp that practices the coding fundamentals of web development and JavaScript libraries such as ReactJS

- · Developed web applications from scratch using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- · Trained in data structures and algorithms
- Collaborated with other developers to build a full stack web application which won award for best capstone project

Support Analyst

City of Toronto I Jul 2021 - Sep 2022

Collaborated with the senior financial analyst and business analyst in the Transit Expansion division to identify and develop solutions to mitigate issues related to transit projects

- Prepared and submitted monthly invoices for Metrolinx transit projects
- · Collaborated with other analysts to organize budget notes
- Supported in migrating transit related project data to Microsoft SharePoint

PROJECTS

Vue Calendar (link)

- Users can create, update, and delete events
- · VueJS, Vuetify, Firebase

Web3 Music Marketplace (link)

- Authenticate users with Metamask and store user data with Firebase
- · ReactJS, Redux, TheAudioDB API

Uniswap Clone (link)

- A clone of Uniswap that allows users to swap ETH with custom tokens
- · NextJS, Solidity, Auth with Metamask